moviego.net 2012-05-23

# Privacy Policy

Privacy policy name.com llc ("name.com") respects your privacy. We want you to use Name.com services with complete confidence in our commitment to serving you and protecting your private information. This Privacy Policy describes how Name.com collects information from users of Name.com's services (the "Services") including those who have accounts (“Customers”) and those who do not (“Visitors”) as well as what we do with the information we collect. Name.com requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

### 
  1. data collection

      1. VISITORS - Visitors to Name.com receive “cookies” to track their movement through our site. This information may include referral URL, IP address, browser type and device type.
      2. CUSTOMERS - When a Visitor opens an account at Name.com we collect personal information including, but not limited to name, e-mail address, billing address, credit card or other payment information as well as a password.

### 
  2. information usage

      1. Browsing information collected from all Visitors is used to diagnose problems and make improvements to our website and services.
      2. Customer information is used to create and maintain accounts as well as contacting Customers in case of any problems with accounts, provide technical support, conduct surveys and other similar activities.

### 
  3. information sharing

      1. Name.com partners with a variety of trusted companies to provide services such as SSL certificates, design and marketing services, etc. In order to expedite and provision such services we must share various levels of Customer information with these partners.
      2. Domain name registrant data is required, by ICANN (Internet Corporation for Assigned Names & Numbers) policy and applicable law, to be complete and correct. This information is published in a publicly searchable database (WHOIS). Certain TLDs (Top Level Domains) allow the utilization of a Privacy Service to obscure personal information while still complying with applicable laws.

### 
  4. exceptions

      1. We reserve the right to, without explicit permission, provide personally identifiable information in the following circumstances:
          1. We believe in good faith that it is necessary to comply with subpoenas, court orders and other legal process as required or permitted by law. 
          2. To report, prevent or assist in the investigation of suspected fraud or other illegal activities or take actions associated with such activities. iii. To enforce the Name.com Terms of Services, establish, exercise or defend our legal rights or as otherwise provided in the User Agreement, AUP or this Privacy Policy.

### 
  5. mailings – upon becoming a name.com customer:

      1. You agree to receive notifications regarding your account including, but not limited to, renewal/expiry notifications and billing notifications. Some of these notices can be turned off from within your account. Please note that note that these notifications are the only notices you will receive from Name.com concerning important activity in your account including, but not limited to, renewal/expiry notifications. Please disable these notices at your own risk. 
      2. You are automatically subscribed to any and all promotional emails and newsletters. You may choose to unsubscribe from these notifications by following the instructions and/or opt-out links provided in the mailings themselves.

### 
  6. adherence to this policy

Name.com takes this privacy policy and the principles herein very seriously. We are committed to abiding by this policy and taking reasonable precautions to ensure that your personal information remains secure. If you have any questions or concerns about the scope, tenants and/or application of this policy please let us know. We welcome your feedback. Please feel free to contact us by phone, email or fax per your preference.

Name.com LLC   
2500 East Second Avenue   
Second Floor   
Denver, Colorado 80206   
Email - support@name.com   
Phone - +1.720.249.2374   
Fax - +1.303.399.3167

Use of our services or products constitutes understanding of and agreement to this policy. Name.com reserves the right to modify this, as well as any other policies and/or agreement at any time.
